Guide to the Kate Millett papers, 1912-2002, bulk 1951-2001 RL.10070
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings and Speeches, 1928-2001, bulk 1968-1998; 42 boxes
  - The Politics of Cruelty (1994), 1985-circa 1997; 4 boxes
    - Material by Date:
      - 1990-1991, Electronic format only: Drafts
        - Chapter 3 draft, file name Gut-ch3b, 1990 Nov. 2 (Disk019) (Box PC2)
        - Chapter 4 draft, file name Gut-ch4, 1990 Nov. 18 (Disk019) (Box PC2)
        - "Notes on the nature of the shameful and secret and what 'shock' really represents," file name Gut-ch6, 1991 Feb. 19 (Disk019) (Box PC2)
        - Draft chapter, file name Gut-ch8, 1991 Feb. 23 (Disk019) (Box PC2)
        - Draft chapter, file name Gut-ch7, 1991 Mar. 30 (Disk019) (Box PC2)
        - Preface, file name Gut-ch1b, 1991 May 2 (Disk019) (Box PC2)
        - Chapter 2 draft, file name Gut-ch2b, 1991 May 6 (Disk019) (Box PC2)
        - Chapter 3 draft, file name Gut-ch3, 1991 May 6 (Disk019) (Box PC2)
        - Chapter 4 draft, file name Gut-ch4b, 1991 May 6 (Disk019) (Box PC2)
        - Draft chapter, file name Gut-ch9, 1991 May 6 (Disk019) (Box PC2)
        - Chapter 2 draft, file name Gut-ch2, 1991 May 7 (Disk019) (Box PC2)
        - Table of contents, file name Gut-cont, 1991 May 7 (Disk019) (Box PC2)
        - Title page, "Captivity and Torture," file name Gut-titl, 1991 May 7 (Disk019) (Box PC2)
        - Preface, file name Gut-ch1, 1991 June 24 (Disk019) (Box PC2)
      - 1990 and 1992, Radha Bharadwaj, Closet Land, script and correspondence (Box PC2)
      - 1991-1992, Hamburger Institut correspondence (Box PC2)
      - 1991-1995 and undated, Correspondence, 2 folders (Box PC2)
      - 1992-1993, Contracts (Box PC2)
      - 1993, Permissions list (Box PC2)
      - 1993, German correspondence (Box PC2)
      - 1993-1994 and undated, Bookstore flyers (Box PC2)
      - 1993-1994, German book reviews (Box PC2)
      - 1993-1995 and undated, North American book reviews (Box PC2)
      - 1994, English book reviews (Box PC2)
      - 1994, Book tour, 2 folders (Box PC2)
      - Circa 1997, Reader's photo collage (Box PC2)
      - Undated, Journal of Women and Therapy pamphlet (Box PC2)
  - Mother Millett (2001), 1991-circa 2000; 2 boxes
    - Undated Drafts:
      - Original typescript, undated, 4 folders (Box MM1)
      - Typescript, undated, 2 folders (Box MM1)
      - Typescript, Parts I and II, undated (Box MM1)
      - Typescript, Part IV, undated (Box MM1)
      - Typescript, last section, undated (Box MM1)
      - Typescript, third or fourth draft, undated, 6 folders (Box MM2)
      - Typescript partial fourth draft, undated (Box MM2)
      - Bound typescript, undated (Box MM2)
      - Amy's Copy with Corrections, undated, 3 folders (Box MM2)
      - Copy 3, undated, 3 folders (Box MM3)
      - Draft fragments, undated (Box MM3)
      - Journal on Helen Millett's illness, undated, 3 folders (Box MM3)
      - Notes ("Dinner with Skippy"), undated (Box MM3)
    - Material by Date:
      - 1991, Electronic format only: Drafts
        - Draft section, file name Mother2, 1991 Mar. 27 (Disk017) (Box MM3)
        - Draft section, file name Mother-3, 1991 May 10 (Disk017) (Box MM3)
        - Part III draft, file name Mother-4, 1991 May 10 (Disk017) (Box MM3)
      - 1991-1992 and undated, Notes and correspondence on Helen Millett's illness (Box MM3)
      - 1998 Summer, Original final version, 3 folders (Box MM3)
  - Other Writings, 1928, 1973-circa 1992, bulk 1973-1992; 4 boxes
    The earliest date, 1928, refers to historical resources used by Millett in writing A.D..
    - Published Books, 1928-1992 and undated; 1973-1992
      - The Prostitution Papers (1973)
        - Undated Drafts:
          - Typescript segments of draft, undated (Box W1)
          - Typescript and manuscript drafts, undated (Box W1)
          - Typescript and manuscript drafts, introduction for Avon paperback edition, undated (Box W1)
          - Manuscript fragments of draft, undated (Box W1)
          - Galley, undated (Box W1)
        - Material by Date:
          - 1972, Editor's revisions (Box W1)
          - 1973 and undated, Fan letters (Box W1)
          - 1973, Netherlands contract (Box W1)
          - 1973, Royalties and finances (Box W1)
          - 1973-1981 and undated, Correspondence, clippings, and reviews (Box W1)
          - 1974, Permissions (Box W1)
      - An Elegy for Sita (1979)
        - Undated Drafts:
          - Typescript and manuscript (photocopy), undated (Box W1)
          - Typescript, undated (Box W1)
          - Typescript, poems and prose, undated (Box W1)
          - Typescript, Prose Elegy for Sita, fair copy, undated (Box W1)
          - Drafts, notes, and correspondence, 1978-1983 and undated (Box W1)
      - Going to Iran (1982)
        - Material by Date:
          - 1979 Mar., News releases (Box W1)
          - 1979-1982 and undated, Reviews and correspondence (Box W1)
          - 1979-1983 and undated, Correspondence and blurbs (Box W1)
          - 1980 and 1982, Contracts (Box W1)
          - 1980, Press release on execution of prostitutes in Iran (Box W1)
          - 1982, German contract (Box W1)
          - 1982 and undated, Correspondence, notes and publicity (Box W1)
          - 1983, Des Femmes royalties (Box W1)
          - Undated, Photos of Iran (photocopies) (Box W1)
      - A.D. (1995)
        - Undated Drafts:
          - Typescript, lawyer's copy, undated, 2 folders (Box W2)
          - Typescript second draft, photocopy, undated, 2 folders (Box W2)
          - Typescript first draft, Parts I and II, undated (Box W2)
          - Typescript, undated, 2 folders (Box W2)
          - Draft A - typescript, undated, 1 of 2 folders (Box W2)
          - Draft A - typescript, undated, 2 of 2 folders (Box W2)
          - Draft B - typescript, undated, 1-5 of 7 folders (Box W2)
          - Draft B - typescript, undated, 6-7 of 7 folders (Box W3)
          - Notes and Ikon article proofs, undated (Box W3)
          - Notes, undated (Box W3)
          - Notes plus odds and ends, undated (Box W3)
        - Material by Date:
          - 1928-1985 and undated, Historical research, photocopied clippings and photos (Box W3)
          - 1984 and undated, Estate settlement correspondence (Box W3)
          - 1984 and undated, Estate settlement papers, 3 folders (Box W3)
          - 1990, Electronic format only: Letter to Aunt Harriet, file names Ad.aha and Adaha, 1990 Sept. 22 (Disk018) (Box W3)
          - 1992, Contract (Box W3)
          - 1992 and undated, Correspondence with Robin Morgan, Ms. Magazine (Box W3)
          - 1992, Electronic format only: Drafts
            - Draft section, file name Kate1, 1992 Apr. 10 (Disk003) (Box W3)
            - Part II, file name Kate2, 1992 Apr. 10 (Disk003) (Box W3)
            - Part IV fragment, file name Kate 4.50, 1992 Apr. 14 (Disk001) (Box W3)
            - Part V fragment, file name Kate 5.50, 1992 Apr. 14 (Disk001) (Box W3)
            - Part VI fragment, file name Kate 6.50, 1992 Apr. 14 (Disk001) (Box W3)
            - Part III, file name Kate3, 1992 Apr. 14 (Disk003) (Box W3)
            - Part III, file name Kate 3.50, 1992 Apr. 14 (Disk002) (Box W3)
            - Part IV, file name Kate4, 1992 Apr. 14 (Disk003) (Box W3)
            - Part 5, file name Kate5, 1992 Apr. 14 (Disk003) (Box W3)
            - Part VI, file name Kate6, 1992 Apr. 14 (Disk003) (Box W3)
            - Draft section, file name Kate 1.50, 1992 Apr. 17 (Disk002) (Box W3)
            - Part II, file name Kate 2.50, 1992 Apr. 18 (Disk002) (Box W3)
    - Articles and Manuscripts, 1962-1990s and undated
      - 1962, "The Second Story" manuscript (Box W3)
      - Circa 1962, "Henry Miller" article, Waseda University Journal, drafts and final (Box W3)
      - 1968-1969 and undated, Token Learning notes and comments (Box W3)
      - 1968-1969 and undated, Token Learning research and manuscript, 5 folders (Box W3)
      - 1970, "Have You Heard About the Rules?" Barnard Bulletin (Box W3)
      - 1970-1971 and undated, "New Book - Tags and Clues" [correspondence, notes, and book tour itineraries] (Box W3)
      - 1973-1998, Publishers' correspondence (Box W3)
      - 1974-1986 and undated, Publishers' correspondence, contracts, and royalty statements (Box W4)
      - 1976-1998 and undated, Requests for editorials and writings (Box W4)
      - 1978-1980, Maryse Holder, Give Sorrow Words - correspondence and typescript of Millett's preface (Box W4)
      - 1979 and undated, Notes, "Progress, Mad Schemes, New Work" (Box W4)
      - 1980 and undated, Going to Iran reading (correspondence and event planning) (Box W4)
      - 1986, Review of two books on Iran (Box W4)
      - 1987 and undated, Loony-bin Trip and A.D. manuscript circulation (Box W4)
      - 1989, Daughters of Simone de Beauvoir, typescript book chapter (Box W4)
      - 1990, Electronic format only: News for Feminist Bookstore News
        - file name Fembknew, 1990 Feb. 9 (Disk019) (Box W4)
      - 1990 and undated, Statement against the Gulf War
        - Statement by Millett and Brenda Fiegan opposing the Gulf War, file name War-no, 1990 Feb. 25 (Disk017); file name War, 1991 Jan. 14 (Disk017) (Box W4)
        - Statement by Phyllis Chesler, Gloria Steinem, Robin Morgan and Millett opposing the Gulf War, file name Warno2, 1991 Feb. 25 (Disk017) (Box W4)
      - 1991, Electronic format only: Millett's comment on Paul and Janet Gotkins' book
        - file name Gotkin, 1991 Mar. 30 (Disk019) (Box W4)
      - 1991, Electronic format only: "Literary Biography," on Millett's difficulties in finding publishers
        - file name Lit-biog, 1991 Apr. 3 (Disk019) (Box W4)
      - 1994, Request for introduction to Influencing Minds (Box W4)
      - 1995, Adventures of a Feminist article (Box W4)
      - 1990s, Book covers, Sexual Politics and Flying (Box W4)
      - Undated, "As I Lay Dying" notes (Box W4)
      - Undated, "Avant Garde Program," typescript draft, Barnard College (Box W4)
      - Undated, Book review, Ronald Sampson, Psychology of Power (Box W4)
      - Undated, "Dad" typescript (Box W4)
      - Undated, Dissertation notes and guide (Box W4)
      - Undated, Drafts about sexism in college education (Box W4)
      - Undated, "Eleven Dollars" typescript (Box W4)
      - Undated, Cynthia MacAdams, Rising Goddess - Millett's typescript introduction (Box W4)
      - Undated, "Montreal" manuscript (Box W4)
      - Undated, "Sherman" manuscript (Box W4)
      - Undated, "South Again" typescript (Box W4)
      - Undated, Women's Liberation and the Women's Colleges manuscript (Box W4)
      - Undated, Women's Liberation and the Women's Colleges typescript drafts (Box W4)
      - Undated, Typescript partial draft for unnamed new book (Box W4)
  - Interviews, 1973-1998; 1 boxes
    - 1973, Seattle Post-Intelligencer interview (Box W4)
    - 1975-1986 and undated, Interviews and correspondence (Box W4)
    - 1975-1991 and undated, Clippings and correspondence (Box W4)
    - 1976 Mar. 16, Vanidades Continental (Box W4)
    - 1977-1987, Sojourner interviews (Box W4)
    - 1980 May 16, Des Femmes en Mouvements (Box W4)
    - 1980, Sappho (Box W4)
    - 1984, La Vie en Rose (Box W4)
    - 1985 and 1991, Quebec and La Vie en Rose (Box W4)
    - 1988-1992, Clipping and correspondence (Box W4)
    - 1989, Interview (Box W4)
    - 1991, Tatyana Mamonova video, correspondence (Box W4)
    - 1996, Paul Cain (Box W4)
    - 1997-1998, Ed Rubin, Art reviews and interview (Box W4)
  - Speeches, 1964-circa 2000; 2 boxes
    - 1964, Education of Kate Millett, Barnard (Box W4)
    - 1968, Sex, Politics, and the New Feminism, Cornell University (Box W4)
    - 1971, Liberation, typescript and notes (Box W4)
    - 1971, Wellesley/Rutgers commencement (Box W4)
    - 1972, California Women's Political Caucus, typescript and manuscript (Box W4)
    - 1973, On behalf of Michael X Malik (Box W4)
    - 1973, On Sculpture, Oberlin College (Box W4)
    - 1974, Gay life and culture (Box W4)
    - 1974-1975, Fall and Winter, Speeches and correspondence (Box W4)
    - 1976 Oct., On being a woman artist, Wisconsin Women in the Arts - notes (Box W4)
    - 1976 Nov., Future Female Sexuality, Houston (Box W4)
    - 1976, Feminist criticism, Modern Language Association conference - notes (Box W4)
    - 1976, Iranian political prisoners (Box W4)
    - 1977, Art and politics, UCLA - outline notes (Box W4)
    - 1977, Sexual politics for women and gays, Hartford (Box W4)
    - Circa 1977, Women's movement in crisis, Toronto - notes and conference materials (Box W4)
    - 1978, Forum on the future (Box W5)
    - 1979 Oct. 14, March on Washington - notes (Box W5)
    - 1980, Against the Draft, Barnard College (Box W5)
    - 1980, Future of feminism, Harvard, International Women's Day (Box W5)
    - 1980, Images of lesbians in literature (Box W5)
    - 1980, Lesbianism and feminism, Liege, Belgium - notes (Box W5)
    - 1980, Women's movement, Luxemburg, Brussells (Box W5)
    - 1981 Apr. 15, Politics of rape, Harvard (Box W5)
    - 1981, West Coast Music Festival (Box W5)
    - 1981, Women in the 1980s, Univ. of North Carolina - Chapel Hill (Box W5)
    - 1982 Mar. 7, Sit'n in USA, Paris, Sorbonne - notes (Box W5)
    - 1982 Mar. The Need for an Opposition Movement, Nevada (Box W5)
    - 1982, Barnard conference on the politics of sexuality - registration materials, speech, and North American Man-Boy Love Association (NAMBLA) publications (Box W5)
    - 1982, Beyond politics: understanding the sexuality of infancy and childhood, Barnard (Box W5)
    - Circa 1982, Notes (Box W5)
    - 1983, Downward mobility, Philadelphia (Box W5)
    - 1983, Feminism in the 1980s, Atlanta (Box W5)
    - 1983, Women's movement, National Organization for Women (Box W5)
    - 1984 Oct., International feminism, Minneapolis (Box W5)
    - 1984 Dec. 12, The women's movement in the 1980s: international feminism and the end of patriarchy, Evelyn Theatre, Westchester (Box W5)
    - 1984, Gays and electoral politics, outside the Denver Convention (Box W5)
    - 1984, Madrid lesbian conference (Box W5)
    - 1984, Women in 1984 (Box W5)
    - 1985 Jan., Irish history/Irish women, Temple Univ. (Box W5)
    - 1985, Bread and roses, North Dakota (Box W5)
    - 1985, Human Rights Convention, Paris (Box W5)
    - 1985, Lunacy and sex roles, Temple Univ. (Box W5)
    - 1985, Papers for colloquium on Simone de Beauvoir, Columbia University (Box W5)
    - 1987, Essentialism, Amsterdam (Box W5)
    - 1987, On aging, Penguin Place, Pa. - speech, notes, and clippings (Box W5)
    - 1987, Sex and society (Box W5)
    - 1989 Feb, On being a woman artist, R.I. School of Design (Box W5)
    - 1990, Electronic format only: "Women and the future," Marist/Macon speech
      - file name Macon, 1990 Mar. 18 (Disk019) (Box W5)
    - 1990, The myth of mental illness
      - "The Myth of Mental Illness," file name Mythment, 1990 May 15 (Disk017) (Box W5)
    - 1990, On being a woman artist (Box W5)
    - 1990, Statement on America Sosa, Co-Madres (Box W5)
    - 1990, To California therapists (Box W5)
    - 1991, Electronic format only: Speech notes on lesbianism
      - file name Lesbian, 1991 Mar. 1 (Disk019) (Box W5)
    - Circa 1991, Gay and lesbian writers (Box W5)
    - 1991, The illusion of mental illness, Ohio essay
      - Speech on The Loony-bin Trip, file name Lbtohio, 1990 Nov. 29 (Disk019) (Box W5)
    - 1993 Apr. 15, Bologna, Italy (Box W5)
    - 1995, On Beijing (Box W5)
    - 1997 Mar. 6, Welfare and feminism, City University of New York, Westfall (Box W5)
    - 1998, Faces on the cover of Time magazine, Smithsonian conference (Box W5)
    - 1999, Impeachment and the Right (Box W5)
    - Undated, Art lecture on sculpture - retrospective (Box W5)
    - Undated, Autobiography - notes (Box W5)
    - Undated, Eroticism and pornography (Box W5)
    - Undated, Gay liberation - notes (Box W5)
    - Undated, Growing up in women's liberation (Box W5)
    - Undated, History of women's movement - notes (Box W5)
    - Undated, The idea of liberation and the future of the women's movement (Box W5)
    - Undated, Images of women in Victorian period - notes (Box W5)
    - Undated, Iran and international feminism, Oct. 5, Long Beach, Calif. - notes (Box W5)
    - Undated, Lesbian society (Box W5)
    - Undated, Liberation of female sexuality (Box W5)
    - Undated, "Mothering," Custody conference (Box W5)
    - Undated, Sex and culture (Box W5)
    - Undated, Sex and literature (Box W5)
    - Undated, Sexual politics and sexual freedom (Box W5)
    - Undated, Situation of the woman writer - notes (Box W5)
    - Undated, Socialism and feminism, debate with Herbert Marcuse, University of California, San Diego (Box W5)
    - Undated, Woman writer, "two MacAlister speeches and Lila's essay" (Box W6)
    - Undated, Women and the arts (Box W6)
    - Undated, Women and the arts/Glassboro - notes (Box W6)
    - Undated, Women and work (Box W6)
  - Engagements, circa 1969-1998; 2 boxes
    - 1969-1971 and undated, Engagements (Box W6)
    - 1970 and undated, Engagements and offers (Box W6)
    - 1970-1971, Tour schedules (Box W6)
    - 1971 and undated, Engagements and offers (Box W6)
    - 1971-1972 and undated, Invitations - declined (Box W6)
    - 1972-1973, Invitations (Box W6)
    - 1973, Abortion Action Coalition of Women, Seattle (Box W6)
    - 1973 and undated, Potential engagements (Box W6)
    - 1973-1974 and undated, Engagements (Box W6)
    - 1973-1993, Engagements and invitations (Box W6)
    - 1974, Gay Resource Center at Evergreen State College (Box W6)
    - 1974-1975 and undated, Engagements (Box W6)
    - 1974-1978 and undated, Engagements - past, 3 folders (Box W6)
    - 1975, Invitations (Box W6)
    - 1975, Women's Writing Conference, Los Angeles (Box W6)
    - 1975-1979 and undated, Possible gigs (Box W6)
    - 1976, Congress on Socio-Sexuality, Rotterdam (Box W6)
    - 1977, Sun Valley Center conference (Box W6)
    - 1977-1979 and undated, Engagements - future (Box W6)
    - 1978, Invitation to Australia (Box W6)
    - 1978, Matriarchist Forum on the Future (Box W6)
    - 1978, Rochester correspondence (Box W6)
    - 1978, Women Reading workshop (Box W6)
    - 1978-1979, Engagements - past, 1 of 2 folders (Box W6)
    - 1978-1979, Engagements - past, 2 of 2 folders (Box W7)
    - 1978-1979 and undated, Gigs (Box W7)
    - 1978-1979 and undated, Naropa Institute, 2 folders (Box W7)
    - 1979, Program Corporation of America (Box W7)
    - 1979, Show and Tell Productions (Box W7)
    - 1979, Vassar Feminist Union invitation (Box W7)
    - 1979-1980 and undated, Gigs (Box W7)
    - 1980, Amsterdam (Box W7)
    - 1980 and undated, European gigs (Box W7)
    - 1980, Panel, Business of Being an Artist, New York (Box W7)
    - 1980-1981, Gigs (Box W7)
    - 1980-1981 and undated, Gigs and notes (Box W7)
    - 1981-1982, Invitation to New Zealand (Box W7)
    - 1982 and undated, Gigs and notes (Box W7)
    - 1982-1983, "The Famous Barnard Conference on Sex," (Box W7)
    - 1982-1983 and undated, Gigs (Box W7)
    - 1983, Alberta Society of Women against Violence (Box W7)
    - 1983, Contract with Phyllis Langer Management (Box W7)
    - 1983-1984 and undated, Gigs (Box W7)
    - 1984, Female sexuality conference, Toronto (Box W7)
    - 1984-1985 and undated, Gigs (Box W7)
    - 1985-1986 and undated, Gigs and notes, 2 folders (Box W7)
    - 1986, Women's conference, Austria (Box W7)
    - 1986-1987 and undated, Gigs (Box W8)
    - 1987, National Association for Rights Protection and Advocacy (NARPA) conference, Detroit (Box W8)
    - 1989-1991 and undated, Engagements - past (Box W8)
    - 1990, Invitation to Buenos Aires (Box W8)
    - 1990-1991 and undated, Engagements - past, 2 folders (Box W8)
    - 1990-1991, Gigs (Box W8)
    - 1990-1991, Possible gigs (Box W8)
    - 1990-1991 and undated, Program Corporation of America (Box W8)
    - 1991, Invitations - refused (Box W8)
    - 1991, OutWrite, San Francisco (Box W8)
    - 1991-1992, Engagements - past (Box W8)
    - 1991-1992 and undated, Gigs (Box W8)
    - 1992-1994 and undated, Gigs (Box W8)
    - 1994, Politics of Reproduction, Carleton (Box W8)
    - 1994, Sirens Workshop Center, Gabriel's (Box W8)
    - 1998, Lammas conference, Washington, D.C. (Box W8)
  - Writings by Others, 1959-2001 and undated; 1969-2001; 3 boxes
    Small collection of drafts and manuscripts sent to Millett. Includes poetry, fiction, and non-fiction works. Author represented by individual manuscripts include Ti-Grace Atkinson, Reza Baraheni (an exiled Iranian author), Phyllis Chesler, Rachel DuPlessis and Ann Snitow, Clara Fraser (socialist feminist), Kay Hagan (NC senator), Shere Hite, Claudia Koontz, The electronic files of writings created by Jennifer Floryan, a close intimate of Millett's, are closed to use for the author's lifetime.
    - Adair, Marguerite, typescript poetry and writing samples, undated (Box W8)
    - Aliesan, Jody, Thunder in the Sun, 1971 (Box W8)
    - Alstad, Diane," Les Liaisons Dangereuses: Hustlers and Hypocrites," 1969 (Box W8)
    - Atkinson, Ti-Grace, speech Violence in the Women's Movement, 1971 and undated (Box W8)
    - Baraheni, Reza, Masculine History typescript, undated (Box W8)
    - Bharadwaj, Radha, Closet Land script, 1992 (Box W8)
    - Chesler, Phyllis, introduction, Woman's Inhumanity to Women typescript, 2001 (Box W8)
    - Clarke, Linda, Men, Women, and the State, dissertation, 1993 (Box W9)
    - Claude, Richard, Scientists and Human Rights typescript, 1970s? (Box W9)
    - Cott, Nancy, Roots of Bitterness galleys, circa 1971 (Box W9)
    - David, Sara Joy, articles on women and psychology, 1974-1980 (Box W9)
    - DeGrand, Alexander paper, 1974 (Box W9)
    - Dellinger, Dave, interview with Nicola Lanzenberg, 1980 (Box W9)
    - Dobbins, Peggy, Kin to Class typescript, 1980 (Box W9)
    - DuPlessis, Rachel Blau and Ann Snitow (eds.), Memoirs of Women's Liberation typescript, 1996, 7 folders (Box W9)
    - Farber, Seth, The Dream Will Not Be Destroyed typescript, 1989 (Box W9)
    - Farber, Seth, chapters from anti-psychiatry typescript, 1990 (Box W9)
    - File under Lesbian Dear Librarian typescript, circa 1970s (Box W10)
    - Electronic format only: Floryan, Jennifer, writings (CLOSED) (Box W10)
    - Fragments from a History of the Duchy of Androvnia, undated (Box W10)
    - Francia, Beatrice Romualdez, Imelda: A Parable of the Sugar Isles, typescript, undated (Box W10)
    - Fraser, Clara, Socialist Feminism, photocopy, 1986 (Box W10)
    - Hacker, Emily, Campaign Speech, typescript poem, 1990 (Box W10)
    - Hagan, Kay, Fugitive Information, typescript, 1992 (Box W10)
    - Hampl, Patricia, St. Paul: Walking, poem, circa 1981 (Box W10)
    - Hartmann, Heidi, The Unhappy Marriage of Marxism and Feminism, typescript, 1979 (Box W10)
    - Hite, Shere, The Hite Report proofs, 1976 (Box W10)
    - Karp, Lila, draft introduction, The Sociology of Women's Literature, undated (Box W10)
    - Electronic format only: Keatings, Anne, letter to Dr. Caughey, 1989
      - file name Caughey!.abk, 1989 July 30 (Disk018) (Box W10)
    - Keatings, Anne, The Farm, dissertation proposal, 1992 (Box W10)
    - Koontz, Claudia, Mothers in the Fatherland chapter, typescript, circa 1985 (Box W10)
    - Littleton, Christine, Sex, Gender, and Sexual Orientation typescript, 1980s? (Box W10)
    - Malszecki, Greg, Fight Like a Man, thesis, 1994 (Box W10)
    - McGrath, Mary, poetry, 1977 (Box W10)
    - Melvin, Janet, Interviews with Honduran Women typescript, 1988 (Box W10)
    - Melvin, Janet, Women of Maize typescript, 1991 (Box W10)
    - Miale, Walter, A Fool's Paradise photocopy, 1978 (Box W10)
    - Miale, Walter, typescript story and clippings, 1988 and undated (Box W10)
    - Miale, Walter (ed.), Notes from a Green World, typescript journal, 1989 (Box W11)